Guide to the American Service Institute Records, ca. 1920-1961 AIS.1963.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Alphabetical Subject Files, III.
  - Intercultural Education, 18.
    - Bibliographies--Intercultural Education and misc. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Intercultural Education Articles (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Evaluation in Intergroup Relations - Some Tentative Instruments, Intergroup Education Workshop, Summer 1946 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - A Sociometric Work Guide For Teachers, June 1947 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Suggested Procedures For Developing Good Intercultural and Interracial Practices in Group Work and Recreation (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Agencies - Report of the Planning Comm. on Cultural Problems in a changing metropolitan community (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Labor, 19.
    - Discrimination in Employment (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Labor and Industry. Program File post war (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Legislation, 20.
    - Codification of the Nationality Laws of the U.S.A. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Legislation - Misc. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Migrant Labor Legislation, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Maps- City-County maps, 21.
    - Maps- City-County maps (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Men's Service Clubs, 22.
    - Junior Chamber of Commerce (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Men's Service Club List (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mental Health, 24.
    - Mental health (Box 13, Folder 16-18)
    - Community Conference on Mental Health, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Minorities, 25.
    - Minorities - General subject matters (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Music, 26.
    - Music - Songs (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Nationality Organizations, 27.
    - lists (Box 13, Folder 22-27)
    - University of Pittsburgh Nationality Rooms (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Naturalization, 28.
    - Naturalization (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Newspapers, 29.
    - Community Press House Organs (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Foreign Language Religious press (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Study of Foreign Language Newspapers, July 1953 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Newspaper Articles - Rackets by Sprigle. newspaper clippings (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Police-Community Relations, 30.
    - Police - Community Relations - Resources file (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Plays, 31.
    - Plays - Play bills (Box 13, Folder 35-37)
  - Prejudice, 32.
    - Prejudice - misc (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Bibliography - records (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - plays (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Program Resources - general (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - role playing in leadership training (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - rumor clinic (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Socio-drama, suggestions for use (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Radio and TV, 33.
    - General correspondence (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Foreign language broadcasters (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Public Relations (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
    - Scripts, 1952-1958 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
    - Radio Programs Bibliographies (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Foreign Language Radio in the U.S. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Radio and Television (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Radio Scripts, 34.
    - Allegheny Valley, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - General Information and Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - General Information and Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" # 2 Our English Heritage (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #3 Our Hispanic Heritage (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #5 Winning Freedom (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #6 The Negro (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #7 French Speaking Peoples and the Netherlanders in the United States (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #8 The Upsurge of Democracy (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #9 Irish in the United States (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #10 Germans in the United States (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #11 Scandinavians in the United States (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #12 Closing Frontiers (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #13 The Jews in the United States (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #14 The Slavs: Russians, Ukrainians, Yugoslavs (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #15 The Slavs: Poles, Czechs, and Slovaks (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #16 the Orientals (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #17 The Italians (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #18 Near Eastern People (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #19 Other Peoples (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #20 Contributions in History (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #21 Contributions in Science (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #22 Contributions in Arts and Crafts (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #23 Contributions to Social Progress (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #24 A New England Town (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #25 An Industrial City (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - "Americans All - Immigrants All" #26 Grand Finale (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - ASI. In cooperation with "Your Government Series" Script #1-6 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - ASI. In cooperation with "Your Government Series" Script #7-11 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - ASI. In cooperation with "Your Government Series" Script #12-15 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - KDKA Intercultural education programs - Correspondence, October 1944 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - KDKA - School of the Air series, "Friends around the World: Scripts 1-6, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - KDKA - School of the Air series, "Friends around the World: Scripts 7-12, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - KDKA - School of the Air series, "Friends around the World: Scripts 13-19, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - KDKA Victory Program, October 1944 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - KDKA Victory Program, November 1944 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - KDKA Victory Program, December 1944 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - KDKA Victory Program, January 1945 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - KDKA Victory Program, February 1945 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - "Mayor's Civic Forum" WWSW, April 15, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Historical Commission. Radio Scripts - Penns. Keystone of Democracy (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Radio programs, correspondence, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Radio and script material (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Radio scripts - WWSW, 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Scripts - misc (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "You Are an American" - radio program. Correspondence, publicity, etc, 1942-1944 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "You are an American - Series #2, November 17, 1942 - December 22, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Race and Interracial, 35.
    - Race Bibliography - Race and cultural contacts (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Race relations. Interracial education. Misc (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Refugees, 36.
    - Allegheny County Committee on Displaced persons - Minutes (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Allegheny County Commission on FEPC (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Articles, speeches - displaced persons (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Bibliography (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Chest X-Ray Committee (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Displaced Persons Committee of the Council of Churches (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Interracial Committee of Allegheny County (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Race Relations Committee of the Council of Churches - correspondence. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Race Relations Committee of the Council of Churches - Misc. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Race Relations Committee of the Council of Churches - Reports and Minutes (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Refugees - misc. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Refugee Resettlement Committee of Allegheny City of Council of Churches, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Social Service Committee - Pittsburgh And Allegheny County X-Ray survey Foundation (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Sones seminar Department of Education - university of Pittsburgh, correspondence. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - U.N. Committee - Pittsburgh Chapter (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Releases, 37.
    - Publicity - correspondence. articles (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
    - Releases - miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 28-31)
    - Scrapbook (Box 15, Folder 32-33)
  - Religion, 38.
    - Bahai - Church (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Bibliography (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Churches - misc. (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Greek Catholic Churches of Western Pennsylvania (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Intercultural Education in Churches (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Interfaith - General Program file (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Jewish Religion (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Released time (Religious Education) (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Religion in social work (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Religious Education Misc. (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Index (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Research studies, 39.
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Committee (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey misc. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, committees (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, correspondence (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, background (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, Pittsburgh (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, publicity (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, recommendations (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, religious organizations (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, schools (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Allegheny County Race Relations Survey, summary (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Commission on race relations. Council of Churches of Christ of Allegheny County (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Commission on returned servicemen. Council of churches (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Committee on higher education - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Religion - Fisk Survey (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Community Service Association: A Project in Community Relations (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Council of Churches Survey, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Council of Industrial and Interracial relations and Committee on Social Education and Action - Presbytery of Pittsburgh (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Race Relations Committee of the Council of Churches, 40.
    - Interpretation of Social Work (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Social Case Work (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Schools, 41.
    - General file (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Desegregation (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools, Division of Extension Education, applicants for naturalization (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 42.
    - Speech - Speeches (Box 16, Folder 25-26)
  - Studies and Surveys, 43
    - First and Second Generation (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Allegheny County (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Audit of International Institute Material on Pittsburgh's Nationality Community, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Supplement to Audit, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Churches (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - The family of the foreign born under restrictive immigration - studies (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - "Immigration and the Forgotten Peoples of Europe" - Arthur E. Lewis (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Is there undue crime among immigrants? Study. By E.H. Sutherland (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Marriage Customs (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - New Americans in Allegheny County. Their interest and needs. Report. Mary E. Hurlbutt (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - New arrival report - studies, 1926-1930 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Preliminary Report for the Steel Valley Regional Planning Committee, Item 1 History and General Factors (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Preliminary Report for the Steel Valley Regional Planning Committee, Item 5 Traffic (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Preliminary Report for the Steel Valley Regional Planning Committee, Item 10 Housing (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Religious study - Interview, Clarke, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Report of the General Secretary of the International Institute of her work with Foreign Communities of Pittsburgh During a Period of ten years vol. 1., 1925-1935 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Report of the General Secretary of the International Institute of her work with Foreign Communities of Pittsburgh During a Period of ten years vol. 2, 1925-1935 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - A Study of Assimilation in Ten Selected Boroughs in Allegheny County by Jessie Bloodworth (East Pittsburgh area), 1930 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - The Sociological aspects of an industrial community by Gwendolyn V. Shand (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
    - Statement concerning the work of the social service group at Ellis Island - Studies, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Study of foreign language organizations. Mrs. Thomas (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Study of Nativity of University of Pgh. Students (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Unfinished Study, Calendar of Holidays, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Unfinished study. Church study, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Volunteers, 44.
    - Volunteers (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Youth, 45.
    - Socio-economic influences of children's learning. Allison Davis (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Program techniques (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Individual and Family Case Files, IV.
  Series IV contains individual case files and has been divided into five sub-series. The first sub-series contains an alphabetical listing of individuals' cases that were closed prior to 1953 -- these deal primarily with citizenship status. Many of these case files provide some detailed narrative of an individual's need for assistance, often to avoid deportation. Similar to the first, the second sub-series contains individuals' case files, although these cases were never considered "closed" and they typically do not contain as much detail. The third sub-series consists of requests for service that did not result in a full case file for 1941-1952. The fourth and fifth sub-series are cases labeled 'McKeesport Records' and 'Pittsburgh Records.' They are similar in nature to the first sub-series but were filed at the two separate office, one in McKeesport the other in Pittsburgh.
  - Individuals' Closed Case Files, 1.
    - A (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Alampi, Joe and Anna (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Albarado, Lucas (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Antonoff (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Argento, John L. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Aschmann, Augusta Edler (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Ashger (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Augerman (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - B (Box 17, Folder 28-32)
    - Babiarz (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Basso, Antonio (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Bacher (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Benedetto (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Bendetto (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Berardi (Lanetti) (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Borrelli (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Boubaris (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Burke, Robert (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - C (Box 17, Folder 42-44)
    - Carranza (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Cristina (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Cuccaro (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - D (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - E (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Esahakiam (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - F (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    - Franchi (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - G (Box 18, Folder 9-12)
    - Grivas (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - H (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
    - Haduch (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
    - Hernadez (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Hruby (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - I (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - J (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - K (Box 18, Folder 22-27)
    - Karnecki (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Kolman, Henryka (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Kontoyiannis (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Kovach (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Kritini (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Kulczycki (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Kundrak (Box 18, Folder 34-35)
    - L (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - Lazorashin, Suzanne (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - M (Box 19, Folder 5-10)
    - Magano, Antonio (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Mappas (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Martinelli, Vincenzo (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Meier (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Moas (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - N (Box 19, Folder 16-17)
    - Naranjo (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Nitta, Jiro (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - O (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Omelczuk (Box 19, Folder 21-24)
    - P (Box 19, Folder 25-27)
    - Pantazis (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Papaj (Pappi) (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Pugliano (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - R (Box 19, Folder 31-32)
    - Rodrigues, Fortunato (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Rodriques (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - S (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
    - Saturley (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Individuals' Open Case Files, 2.
    - Abarotin, Eugen (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Abdullah, Abdi (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Abdullah, Mohamed (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Abraham, Joseph (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Abrasheff, Kiril (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Ackelson, F D (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Adamek, Edward (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Adamek, William (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Adams (Ademenko) John (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Ahlgren, Mona Ingegard (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Aladuni (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Albert, Karl (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Albert, Sam (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Almanza (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Amafa (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Anastasio, Dominick (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Balouris, Dhemestocles (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Batanoff, Kiril E (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Baustista, Vincente (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Byerly-Butrykowska (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Caddle, Kenneth (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Cannella, Giacomo (Adelina) (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Caporale, Tullio (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Casarez, Francisco (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Cervellera, Salvatore (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Chernay (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Cherny (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Cicco, Anthony (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Cimarosa, Domenico (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Cipriani, Lena (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Colussi, Stefano (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Comparelli, Antonio Angelo (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Contaridis, Xanthos (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Corsaro, Elario (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Countouris, Jerry (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Cvetkovich (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Dalson, Mr. and Mrs. George (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - D'Anieelo, Daniel (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - DePascale, Peter (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - DePellegrini, Aronne (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Deramo, Domenico (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - DeVonish, Joseph (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Diakopoulos, Demetrios (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - DiNardo, Mrs. Adam (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Dioguardi, Guido (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Djordjevic (Djordjevich), Ilja (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Dougherty, Mrs. Simone Marie (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Dragonosky, John (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Economan, George (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Engez, Selahattin (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Euch, Mrs. Anna (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Evans (Ivanoff), Nicola (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Falva, Serafino (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Fanok (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Fava, Rosario (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Fielidng, Mrs. Margaret (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Forsythe (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Gallay, Nick (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Garces (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Gatto, Racco (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Gelb, Leopold (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Gentile (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - George, James (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Georgieff and Christoff (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Gorup, Ivan (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Grafas, Mrs. Rose M (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Grencarski, Mara (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Grujic, Mr. and Mrs. Nick (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Handrabura, Mihai (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Hanke, Mrs. Laura (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Heyman, Mr. and Mrs. Gustav C (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Himelreich, Mrs. Gizela (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Homoki, Mrs. Barbara (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Hrubec, Zdenek (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Ikonnikow, Wladimir (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Ivanoff, Della (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Ivanoff, Vladimir M., Christina, Michael V (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Ivanoff, Ivan (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Jackson, Lee (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Jeliniek, Victor (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Jones, James Wiliamsdore (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Jusys, Joseph (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Kakiopulos, Sophia (Box 20, Folder 89)
    - Kalas, John (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Kampetis, James (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Karchuck, Mrs. George (Box 20, Folder 92)
    - Kazalas, George (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - Kazonich, Peter (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Kehaioff, George (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - Kenny, Francis J. (Box 20, Folder 96)
    - Klesznicki, William (Box 20, Folder 97)
    - Koening, Roman T. (Box 20, Folder 98)
    - Kokalis, Jerry (Box 20, Folder 99)
    - Kokinakis, Jim E. (Box 20, Folder 100)
    - Kominos, Mike George (Box 20, Folder 101)
    - Konstant, Stanley (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - Konstantinov, Traiko (Box 20, Folder 103)
    - Koutsoutis, Elias (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Krug, Mrs. Karoline (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Kudlik, Anna (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Lamanna (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Lamantia, Joseph (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Lardas, Mr. Kyriacos (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Laysoun, Yousef Eid (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Lazarean, George (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Charles (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Livanos, Michael (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Loncharich, March (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Macarona, Manolis Demetriu (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Macek (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Della Maestra, Mr. Guiseppe (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Makris, William (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Mandsenko, Constantine (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Martinez, Pablo (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Mastrogianopoulos, Peter (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Mellis, George (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Mellia, John and Michael (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Mendler, Oliver J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Menin, Victor (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Mezkel (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Miskalis (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Mitich, Milorad (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Mollica, Pete (Mrs.) (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Moskes, Nikoldos (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Mularz (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Nadai, Herbert (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Neely, Clarence and Nellie (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Nomiden, Charles (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Obade (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Okolowicz (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Omodio, Joseph and Mary (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Ostasalski, Constantine (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Pagonis, Nicholas (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Pampina, Luigi (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Panamarew, Ermoli (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Panza, Gino Ettore (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Papdopoullon, Melis and Gregoria (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Papas, Peter. A (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Pataky, John Steve (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Paterakis, Anthony (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Perry (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Peszko, Theresa (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Petcoff, Mr. Nicola C (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Pekevicienne, Mrs. Povilas (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Petruzzi (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Picoolo, Rev. D. Raffolle (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Pido, John (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Pisaravska, Maria. Shkurat, Nicholas and Euhenia (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Pope, Mr. Michael (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Popytak (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Pretnick, George (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Prohorow, Vasily (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Protopapas, Phillips (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Pytiak, Peter (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Rajkowska (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Romanus, Nassima (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Ross, Joseph (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Rotunda (Mazza) (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Sacoulas (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Savla, John (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Santiago, Philip (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Sarabia, Alfonso and Olga (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Schroter, Albert S (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Schulze, Rudolf and Henry (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - Scopelitis, John (Box 21, Folder 68)